<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<seiscomp>
        <module name="sceqcct" category="texnet" author="Texas Seismological Network (TexNet)">
                <description>
                        EQCCT module
                </description>
                <configuration>
                        <parameter name="stations" type="list:string">
                                <description>
                                    Define the list of stations that are allowed to process. Fotmat: NET.STA
                                </description>
                        </parameter>
                        <parameter name="whiteChanns" type="list:string">
                                <description>
                                    Define the list of channles types that are allowed to process. Example: HH, CH
                                </description>
                        </parameter>
                        <group name="eqcct">
                                <parameter name="Pmodel" type="string">
                                        <description>
                                            EQCCT model to detect P phases.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="Smodel" type="string">
                                        <description>
                                            EQCCT model to detect S phases.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="windowLength" type="int" default="60">
                                        <description>
                                            Define the data window length in seconds to send to eqcct.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="probThreshold" type="double" default="0.001">
                                        <description>
                                            Minimum probability to reach to send a new pick.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>              
                                <parameter name="timeShift" type="int" default="30">
                                        <description>
                                            Define the time in seconds to overlap with the previous window.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="stasBulk" type="int" default="5">
                                        <description>
                                            Number of stations to send at a time to eqcct.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="startLatency" type="int" default="60">
                                        <description>
                                            Define time in seconds to wait before sending the first data packet to eqcct.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>              
                                <parameter name="timeRemoveTrace" type="int" default="600">
                                        <description>
                                            Maximum time in seconds to wait before remove traces from the processing stream.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="eqcctPthr" type="double" default="0.001">
                                        <description>
                                            Minimum probability to reach to send a new P pick.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="eqcctSthr" type="double" default="0.002">
                                        <description>
                                            Minimum probability to reach to send a new S pick.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="eqcctOverlap" type="int" default="0">
                                        <description>
                                            If set the detection and picking are performed in overlapping windows.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="eqcctBatchSize" type="int" default="1">
                                        <description>
                                            Batch size. This wont affect the speed much but can affect the performance. A value beteen 200 to 1000 is recommended.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="gpuID" type="int" default="0">
                                        <description>
                                            Id of GPU used for the prediction. If using CPU set to None.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="gpuLimit" type="int" default="1">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the maximum percentage of memory usage for the GPU.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                        </group>
                        <group name="ray">
                                <parameter name="numCPUs" type="int" default="5">
                                        <description>
                                            Number of CPUs allocated for running the run_picker() to create the time chunks.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="maxTimeTasksQueue" type="int" default="1">
                                        <description>
                                            Number of given time chunks that are sent to the predictor at the same time. If your time chunk length is equal to one this should be one as well.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="maxStsTasksQueue" type="int" default="1">
                                        <description>
                                            Number of given stations that are sent to the predictor at the same time. This value cannot be greater than eqcct.stasBulk.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                        </group>
                        <group name="qcheck">
                                <parameter name="latUncTHR" type="int" default="20">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the latitude uncertainty threshold. Above this value, the origin evaluation status is FalseOrgEvalStat, and below is TrueOrgEvalStat.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="lonUncTHR" type="int" default="20">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the longitude uncertainty threshold. Above this value, the origin evaluation status is FalseOrgEvalStat, and below is TrueOrgEvalStat.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="depthUncTHR" type="int" default="20">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the depth uncertainty threshold. Above this value, the origin evaluation status is FalseOrgEvalStat, and below is TrueOrgEvalStat.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="depthTHR" type="int" default="20">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the depth threshold. Above this value, the origin evaluation status is FalseOrgEvalStat, and below is TrueOrgEvalStat.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="azGapTHR" type="int" default="270">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the azimuthal gap threshold. Above this value, the origin evaluation status is FalseOrgEvalStat, and below is TrueOrgEvalStat.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="region" type="string" default="none">
                                        <description>
                                            The BNA file defining regions (closed polygons) or tuple with 4 elements. Inside this region, the origin evaluation status is TrueOrgEvalStat, and outside is FalseOrgEvalStat. If this is set to none, then the origin location will not be checked against any polygon.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="TrueOrgEvalStat" type="int" default="5">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the origin evaluation status to use when the origin fulfills all quality thresholds. Use integers from 0 to 5. Each integer means following next list: 0=preliminary, 1=confirmed, 2=reviewed, 3=final, 4=rejected, 5=reported.
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                                <parameter name="FalseOrgEvalStat" type="int" default="4">
                                        <description>
                                            Set the origin evaluation status to use when the origin does not fulfill one or more quality thresholds. Use integers from 0 to 5. Each integer means following next list: 0=preliminary, 1=confirmed, 2=reviewed, 3=final, 4=rejected, 5=reported
                                        </description>
                                </parameter>
                        </group>
                </configuration>
        </module>
</seiscomp>